<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Test</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Test</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 15:03:11 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Haha Ilyes funny</title>
      <link>/posts/testagain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 15:03:11 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/testagain/</guid>
      <description>Testing this is s hugo test this was automatically generated from a .md to html by using paramaters to style and tags
h1 h2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tensorflow and Gsteam</title>
      <link>/posts/tensorflowpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 15:03:11 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tensorflowpost/</guid>
      <description>TensorFlow inference with GStreamer GStreamer GStreamer is a framework for creating streaming media applications and plugins:
 Application programmers can build media pipeline easily without writing a single line of code using its extensive set of plugins. Plugin programmers can use its clean and simple API to create self-contained plugins. It also provides a set of extensible base classes that can be use by object inheritance.  Check more about GStreamer on its official documentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Fractals sierplinkski triangle for -- Beginners</title>
      <link>/posts/py-frac-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/py-frac-01/</guid>
      <description>python setup Imports we will be using PyLab for this for mapping and We will use numpy for math with py
import numpy as np import pylab from random import randint </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax</title>
      <link>/posts/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>/posts/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>/posts/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.
In this example we will be using KaTeX
 Create a partial under /layouts/partials/math.html Within this partial reference the Auto-render Extension or host these scripts locally. Include the partial in your templates like so:
  {{ if or .Params.math .Site.Params.math }} {{ partial &amp;#34;math.html&amp;#34; . }} {{ end }}  To enable KaTex globally set the parameter math to true in a project&#39;s configuration To enable KaTex on a per page basis include the parameter math: true in content files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/posts/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.
The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.
To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site’s configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.
The Emoji cheat sheet is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.
 N.B. The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>